addforums.com 2010-05-19

# Privacy Policy - ADD Forums - Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder Support and Information Resources Community

This privacy statement covers [www.addforums.com](http://www.addforums.com/) and all of its properties and subsidiaries. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users' privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices to our users. ADD Forums is the sole owner of all information collected from our site.

Our server automatically logs information about our visitors, including but not limited to IP address, the page(s) they visited, their HTTP referrer, their browser and version, age groups, geographic location, the duration of their visit, etc. No personally identifiable is available to any third parties.

Additionally, users are required to register to use our message board software. During registration, users are required to provide certain information, including an email address and a password. This information is never given or sold to any third party. Passwords for use with our message board software are encrypted in our database. No one can get them, no one can decipher them. "Personal Messages" or "Private Messages" sent and received using our message board software are considered private. "Private messages" and "Personal messages" are still subject to the same rules and regulations that govern the public areas of the message boards (i.e. harrassment, misconduct, advertising), and said rules will be enforced, if a complaint is received.

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, ADD Forums, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (i.e. email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users accounts or personally identifiable information. This can be done by e-mailing [admin@addforums.com](mailto:admin@addforums.com).

__________________  
To review the ADD Forums Guidelines, please [**click here.**](http://www.addforums.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=75)  
  
The end is near...I don't have time to shoe shop for Andi! [](http://www.boardoo.com/)
